# **Alvieto Haykal**

Surabaya, Indonesia | <a href="mailto:haykalcs@gmail.com">haykalcs@gmail.com</a> | (62) 822-3489-7335 <a href="mailto:linkedin.com/in/alvietomhf">linkedin.com/in/alvietomhf</a> | alvietomhf.qithub.io

# **Fullstack Developer**

A skilled, competent, and diligent individual, specializing in the fullstack web development (Laravel - NodeJS/Express/Nest - ReactJS). For the last 2 years, I have been developing applications using PHP, JavaScript, and TypeScript programming languages. I love coding and am interested in solving problems while coding. I've hands on in all stages of the programming cycle, from planning to development and deployment. No two days are the same for me; my tasks may involve analyzing algorithms, altering code, fixing bugs, brainstorming ideas for integrating new systems.

# **Experience**

# Web Developer, PT Bimasakti Multi Sinergi (Sept 2022 - present)

- Maintain and develop features SpeedCash
- Maintain and develop features TiketKAI
- Maintain and develop features Internal Control Panel System

### Backend Developer, Runshop (Aug 2021 - Jan 2022)

- · Add bank mutation checker
- Integration with payment gateway
- Integration with notification service
- Develop multiple modules

# Backend Developer, PT Kipa Teknologi Indonesia (Jan 2021 – Feb 2021) Internship

Develop a project called "Sadean" including:

- Authentication module using JWT
- Customer module
- Product module
- Utility for sending email and firebase push notification

# Skills

- Laravel (Expert)
- NodeJS/Express (Expert)
- NestJS (Intermediate)
- ReactJS (Intermediate)
- Golang/Gin (Intermediate)
- PHP, JavaScript (Expert)
- HTML, CSS (Expert)
- MySQL, PostgreSQL (Expert)
- Docker (Intermediate)
- GitHub, Gitlab CI/CD (Intermediate)

# **Certifications**

Backend Developer Expert (Dicoding Indonesia, 2021)

# **Education**

- Universitas Negeri Surabaya, Teknik Informatika (2018 2022)
- SMA A. Wahid Hasyim Tebuireng Jombang (2015 2018)

#### Languages

- English Fluent
- Bahasa Indonesia Native